microlifeline.net 2010-11-02

# Microlifeline-[Privacy Policy]

****

MicroLifeLine values the privacy of information pertaining to its associates & members. We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our site or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number,mobile no to any outside sources.

This Privacy Policy covers MicroLifeLine's treatment of personally identifiable information that MicroLifeLine collects when you are on the MicroLifeLine site, and when you use MicroLifeLine 's services. This policy also covers MicroLifeLine's treatment of any personally identifiable information that MicroLifeLine's business partners share with MicroLifeLine. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MicroLifeLine does not own or control, or to people that MicroLifeLine does not employ or manage.

We will not use information about you without your permission and will provide the means for you to manage and control the information that you have provided.

MicroLifeLine collects personally identifiable information when you register for an MicroLifeLine account, when you use certain MicroLifeLine products or services, when you visit MicroLifeLine pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. MicroLifeLine may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.   
When you register with MicroLifeLine, we ask for your first name, last name, country, state, city, email, birth date, and mobile no with country code. Once you register with MicroLifeLine and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. You will also select an User ID and password that you will use to login to the MicroLifeLine services. Your User ID cannot be changed .   
Also during registration, you have the ability to register your mobile phone or email to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your receiving modes. You must also provide the validation code that MicroLifeLine sends to your mobile phone or email to ensure that the service you are registering does belong to you.   
MicroLifeLine may also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, MicroLifeLine cookie information and the page you requested. MicroLifeLine uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

MicroLifeLine will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Notwithstanding the foregoing, MicroLifeLine may sell and/or transfer you personally identifiable information to an affiliate and to any successor-in-interest as a result of a sale of any part of MicroLifeLine's business or upon the merger, reorganization or consolidation of MicroLifeLine with another entity on a basis that MicroLifeLine is not the surviving entity. For the purposes of this paragraph, "affiliate" means any person directly, or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with MicroLifeLine. The term "control," as used in the immediately preceding sentence, shall mean with respect to any person, the possession, directly or indirectly, of the power, through the exercise of voting rights, contractual rights or otherwise, to direct or cause the direction of the management or policies of the controlled person. As used in this Privacy Policy, the term "person" includes any natural person, corporation, partnership, limited liability company, trust, unincorporated association or any other entity   
MicroLifeLine will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:   
We have your consent to share the information; or We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of MicroLifeLine to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);   
We respond to court orders or legal process; or   
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the MicroLifeLine Terms and Conditions or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

Advertising   
We may use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Cookies  
Certain information is required for registration, but other requested information is optional and may be given at your discretion. Some MicroLifeLine services may require that you provide personally identifiable information. We may use "cookies" to let you use our services more easily, and to let us keep track of certain statistical information that helps us improve our site   
Cookies may also be used by us to remember users, estimate our audience size, track number of entries in some of our promotions, and contests and measure certain traffic patterns.   
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

MicroLifeLine may, in its sole discretion, set and access MicroLifeLine cookies on your computer.   
MicroLifeLine may allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MicroLifeLine cookies.   
MicroLifeLine may, in its sole discretion, use techniques that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with MicroLifeLine products and services 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

Changes in Privacy Policy  
MicroLifeLine may amend this policy from time to time, at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting the changes here on these Privacy Policy pages or one may check from the website. If you have more questions or comments, please send your feedback to us at [enquiry@microlifeline.net](mailto:enquiry@microlifeline.net)

MicroLifeLine Corporate. Privacy Policy 

Copyright © 2010 MicroLifeLine, All rights reserved.
